Nahim Bin Reza Udoy

Full-Stack Web Developer

Has 1 year of hands-on experience using **Laravel**. Dedicated to continuous development, implementation, and adaptation with new technologies to maximize development efficiency. Abilities to effectively self-manage with independent projects as well as team player inside the collaborative team set or decide by an organization.

nahimbinrezaudoy@gmail.com

01724191079

01124131013

nahimudoy.netlify.app/

_

github.com/NahimBinRezaUdoy

EDUCATION

Computer Science and Engineering Daffodil International University

2018 - 2021 Result: 3.90

Science

Anonda Mohan Collage, Mymensingh

2014 - 2018 Result: 4.57

Science

Mymensingh Zilla School

2014 Result: 5.00

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

AALO Limited

07/2021 - 09/2021

Contact: 7 Website Development in Laravel

Jr Web Application Developer Datatech BD Ltd.

01/2022 - Present

Dhaka

Datatech BD Ltd is a Bangladeshi software firm that specializes in software development. Since May 2019, the company has offered high-quality services

Achievements/Tasks

Web Application Development

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Social-Work Base Website

 On this website, Admin can create blogs, events, images (based on any issue). Users can see those and can contact Admin and help if the user wants.

Movie Website

 On this website, we can see the latest movie details, movie trailers, Search any movie.

Survey Website

 Features like create multiple questions, share those & saw results.

Linkers Website

 On this website, we can store links, share those with others, and count visitors.

Post Sharing Website

 This is a Post sharing website where we can create Post, can follow someone.

Status Sharing Website

 This is a status-sharing website where we can create status, like, unlike others status.

Educational Server (Running)

Restaurant Management System

 This whole project was developed in the Java programming language.

Fake News Prediction

 This project was developed in AI where we can predict that the news is Fake or Real.